literally are the epitome of what white
supremacy does to black people sits on
the outside and judges when you're
actually black and you supposed to be
woke black even though you're in
Calabasas with the Kardashians you're
clearly out of touch you're clearly
delusional and I don't care smart people
are still stupid and stupid people sound
smart and somewhere in that you'll
figure out which one you are but you
don't have to worry about being invited
to anything else over here you don't
have autism you're fake you're late and
you're a fraud and so when you get mad
at people for getting mad at you just
understand that everybody don't have the
right barbecue sauce to come to the
picnic and your potluck dish is nothing
but potato salad raisins I'm looking at
a black woman who is angry who is mad
and who is losing grip with reality
because she's caught up in her own [ __ ]
and people aren't going to tell you that
because they're afraid of your rant I
will rant go back and forth with you day
and night but unfortunately I'm running
for office so I can change the
communities that I wake up in while you
just go to your Tik Tok and talk tick
your life away we're not feeling that
over here and it's sad that you had to
do that but you can't be
mad that on the same day you called me
to thank me or no the same day you
called me to tell me that a woman in
Grenada told you that my interview with
you was the best and get mad on the same
day that I criticize you for saying that
you have autism but you were clinically
diagnosed by yourself when I have a
nephew that just graduated high school
with autism so for us that those of us
that have people in our lives that have
autism that's a real thing that my
sister lives with on a day-to-day basis
is a real thing when we see people like
you make a mockery out of it and sound
like a fool then
[Music]
go I'm going to Dish you right now
the witch
[Music]
doctor hey how y'all doing what's going
on Welcome to the messy sweet spot and
honey when I tell you it's a lot of mess
going on with Jason Lee Tiffany and
Amanda seals you guys don't know Jason
tells us that Amanda seals is jealous of
Tiffany hadish Tiffany had it she's
getting invited to places that Amanda
only wish she could be in and she cannot
take Tiffany he says the only reason
while Amanda criticized his event was
because Tiffany was hosting and he
cannot she cannot stand a Tiffany but
you know am man Jason if you his friend
one thing he's going to ride for you
he's going to go back for you and Amanda
um she criticized Jason Lee event and a
lot of people that was there and when I
tell you he read Amanda seals
to girl he just read her down I want you
guys to look at this and I want to know
what you guys think about this make sure
you guys like share and subscribe to
this YouTube channel the messy Sweet
Spot check this out Tiffany has a new
book called Tiffany has has a new book
called I'mma curse you with joy I'm not
going to curse you with joy I'm just
going to keep it real um I have an
affection for Amanda SS and grew respect
for Amanda SS for what she went through
with the real because I knew what that
was or whatever at least I thought I
knew what it was it's instances like
what I've saw with Amanda over the last
month play out that makes me start going
H right like I know Issa Reay personally
and I think Issa re is dope I think
she's sweet she's nice she has the most
beautiful skin and she's the best person
to sit next to on a flight uh I don't
have any negative things to say about
her and have never really heard anything
negative about Isa in fact everybody
that knows her loves her Charlamagne I
mean I can go on and on so I've given my
platform to you Amanda to tell your side
I've come to your house I sent you
flowers uh apologizing for my schedule
being mixed up and me not being there
you you acknowledge that on your show I
came to your show I let you ask me any
question you want I answered it all the
way that I felt truthfully you came on
my show you answered your question you
know I I believed we had this
relationship I know that Amanda was
upset that I question Her self-
diagnosis of autism and her backtracking
of it all online she's really good at
gaslighting social media for clicks when
I really don't even think she pays
attention to half the [ __ ] she's saying
at this point you stand for black
Progressive movements but then you go
and post a photo of our invitation to
you to this black owned award show that
you cried about when Essence did the
article on you and you said that you
don't get invited to any blackowned
award shows I invited you and you took
the invitation and put it on your on
your um what's that thing on your
patreon account with laughing emoji
because you hate Tiffany hadish you're
jealous of Tiffany hadish you are mad at
Tiffany hadish because she's invited in
spaces that you get thrown out of and
you're just not a happy person but when
I saw you make a light of the fact that
we invited you we me and Tiffany
literally talked about intentionally
inviting you to the award show so you
could be included and you made a joke
out of that then you went on social
media and you attacked thean without
having even seen
her speech on how she delivered that
moment for Jonathan which was which is
going to be very big for our culture you
attacked and criticized as an outsider
you literally are the epitome of what
white supremacy does to black people
sits on the outside and judges when
you're actually black and you supposed
to be woke black even though you're in
Calabasas with the Kardashians you're
clearly out of touch you're clearly
delusional and I don't care smart people
are still stupid and stupid people sound
smart and somewhere in that you'll
figure out which one you are but you
don't have to worry about being invited
to anything else over here you don't
have autism you're fake you're late and
you're a fraud and so when you get mad
at people for getting mad at you just
understand that everybody don't have the
right barbecue sauce to come to the
picnic and your potluck dish is nothing
but potato salou raisins I'm looking at
a black woman who is angry who is mad
and who is losing grip with reality
because she's caught up in her own [ __ ]
and people aren't going to tell you that
because they're afraid of your rant I
will rant go back and forth with you day
and night but unfortunately I'm running
for office so I can change the
communities that I wake up in while you
just go to your Tik Tok and talk tick
your life away we're not feeling that
over here and it's sad that you had to
do that but you can't be
mad that on the same day you called me
to thank me or no the same day you
called me to tell me that a woman in
Grenada told you that my interview with
you was the best and get mad on the same
day that I criticize you for saying that
you have autism but you were clinically
diagnosed by yourself when I have a
nephew that just graduated high school
with autism so for us that those of us
that have people in our lives that have
autism that's a real thing that my
sister lives with on a day-to-day basis
is a real thing when we see people like
you make a mockery out of it and sound
like a fool then go and Gaslight black
people people in saying how you're never
welcome into black spaces then when you
do you make a mockery of it then you go
online and you literally attack a black
woman for what you believe she's doing
when you fail to show up to see it for
yourself you're a joke and I'm sorry if
that hurts but it probably doesn't
because you look like an emotionless
person that somehow cries herself to
sleep with fake tears okay and that's
how I feel about you and the situation
and it was it was surprising that I'm
not a subscriber to your patreon because
I don't subscribe to trash but somebody
that is subscribed sent it to me to show
me what you did and they were disgusted
by
it sad do better do you want to say
anything yeah you can be very loud and
very wrong at the same time and then to
make people pay to hear you be loud and
wrong is
sick you weren't there for the moment
you shouldn't have spoke on it I I'm
very disappointed cuz I used to love
Amanda Sals and then it's like you you
tout yourself as wanting to be black
Excellence no wonder you can't get in
the gold party now you can't get into
the copper party you can't get in our
party you can't get in Isa Ray party you
know it's like every part but you know
what you'll somehow be the victim you're
going to turn this into a look at this
big old black gay man attacking me nah
you got up there put your big old face
right in that screen and had the
audacity to attack Ayan without even
knowing the facts like what's woke about
that you don't even don't even I
wouldn't this isn't even about an
apology because the fact that you
criticized a blackowned
black created black targeted black
Excellence based event because you had
your own issues with Tiffany hattis now
don't have me get Tiffany in here and
talk about all the jealousy and lies and
the and the way that you're you know
your your personal issues with Tiffany
because that's what you were really
shading you just didn't probably didn't
think about it being my event because it
said Tiffany hadish hosting the impact
words and you did a whole joke about
that
so I really don't
know what to say other
than do better all right we'll move
along before